pennyjobs.com 2011-05-31

# Privacy policy | PennyJobs

Updated: January 15, 2008

Your right to privacy is very important to us. We recognize that providing us with personal information on this Web Site is an act of trust. Therefore, we have created this privacy policy to protect your personal information. This policy only pertains to this Web Site owned and operated by Kaylib Inc. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of any other Web Site that you visit. By accessing this Web Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy policy.

Information collected on this Web Site will be used according to the following guidelines:

Contact Us

Our 'Contact Us' page allows you to contact us directly with any questions, comments, concerns, or requests that you may have. The information you provide is only used to respond to your inquiry and to formulate frequently asked questions. We do not provide any information to third parties.

Use of Personal Information

We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advanced permission or unless ordered by a court of law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served to us. Information submitted to us is available only to employees who manage this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you e-mails based on your request or related to your account. 

Links

This Web Site contains links to third party Web Sites. We encourage you to visit these Web sites to learn about their privacy policies as they may differ from ours.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update this privacy policy. When we do, we will also revise the "updated" date at the top of the page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. If you have any questions or complaints about any uses of information, or about this policy in general, you may contact us by navigating to our 'Contact Us' page in the menu.
